I'm hungry...
お腹が空く...
It's a moment.
一瞬です
hot?
暑い?
It's hot.
暑いね
I was sweating.
汗かいたもんね
A quick shower?
一瞬シャワー?
Shall we take a shower?
シャワーしようか?
Was it hot?
暑かった?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It was hot.
暑かったです
Let's stand up and let it flow.
立って流そうね
ERROR
本当に暑かった
On the street in winter, I was taking a shower,
冬の夜通り、 シャワーを浴びていたら、
Wash.
洗いなさい
I wash my seat carefully before I sit down.
席を前に、 気をつけて、 洗っています
Are you hungry?
お腹が空いた?
You feel better in the shower.
シャワーで気持ちよくなってますね
Also
また
I have to rise.
上 がらないといけない
You feel better in the shower.
シャワーで気持ちよくなってますね
Seriously?
マジで?
Does that mean it doesn't count?
数えないってこと?
It's hard to do here because it's small and it's hot.
ここ狭くてやりにくいからさ、暑いし
Once again in a wide area.
広いところでもう一度
Let's have sex freely.
のびのびとセックスしよう
It's fine if it's a spacious place.
広いところですればいいよね